# Jordan Fisher

Software Developer, specialising in Android

linkedin.com/in/jordanspencerfisher

gitlab.com/thementalgoose



jordanfisher.io (calendar) thementalgoose@gmail.com



**ABOUT** 

Highly motivated software developer (specialising in Android) working for Roller Agency in Nottingham, looking to create

# SKILLS

Java 7 years, JSP / JSTL, JavaFX, Crypto, Servers / Sockets / Java3D **Spring Boot** Hibernate **Android** Realm, Retrofit, Glide, Firebase, ROOM, LibGDX, Espresso Python **C#** Console/GUI VCS Git/SVN **Firebase** Realtime DB, functions, hosting **CI/CD** Bitbucket Pipelines / Travis CI **Unit Testing Cucumber MEAN stack** Mocha Chai, Mongoose Typescript PHP Laravel / WordPress SQL/NoSQL HTML(5) CSS(3) JS Bootstrap / Flexbox / twig GTM

awesome software. Passions include technology, interests in software, gadgets, f1, skating and snowboarding.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Roller Agency

Oct 2017 - today

## **Software Developer**

Building modules in 2 existing android apps and firebase angular2 projects. Analytics tracking through websites using GTM and GA.

#### **Roller Agency**

Jun 2016 - Jun 2017

## **Android App Developer**

Responsible for 5 android apps for public and private clients, including LibGDX game, most deployed to play store. Performed consultancy work for medical-based tech company for android based SDK for business logic.

#### **Personal Development**

Jun 2013 - today

## **Projects / Freelance**

First android app during A level project (Driving Tutor) Completed 3 websites on freelance basis University has seen me make static / full stack web apps (Spring MVC), experience with Haskell, Python, PROLOG, R, 3D simulations, games.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **University of Leicester**

Sept 2014 - Sept 2018

#### **Computer Science Degree BSc**

1st Class

## **Lutterworth College**

Sept 2010 - Sept 2014

#### A Levels

Maths (A\*) Computing (A) Physics (A)

#### **ADDITIONAL**

## **Harvey Furniture Store**

Jun 2015 - Sept 2015

# **Quality Control Inspector**

Validated quality of returned goods for clearance. Position of high responsibility, required heavy teamwork / communication / skills.

## **Castle Freight Ltd**

Apr 2012 - Sept 2014

#### (Senior) Night Loader

Senior Night Loader and general warehouse management. Teamwork and time critical environment, managed a small team before leaving